https://www.halosleep.com/privacy-cookies

Return to top
FREE SHIPPING on all orders over $50!
Menu
New ArrivalsBassiNest® Newborn InsertDisney™ Baby by HALO®Fall Winter 2020ShopBassiNests®Swivel SleepersTwin SleeperGlide SleeperAccessoriesSleepSack® CollectionSwaddlesEasy TransitionWearable BlanketsEarly WalkerBig KidsSleepSack® Platinum CollectionSwaddlesWearable BlanketsGift SetsCollaborations & CollectionsDisney™ Baby by HALO®Fall Winter 2020GiftsGift SetsGift CertificateSaleAll SaleSale DreamNest™Sale SleepSack® CollectionDiscover HALOOur StoryBassiNests®Swivel SleepersTwin SleeperGlide SleeperAssembly VideoFAQsSleepSack® CollectionSwaddlesEasy TransitionWearable BlanketsEarly WalkersFAQsHealthcare ProfessionalsHealthcare ProductsBassiNest® Hospital SeriesTrulyPreemie SleepSack® SwaddleHealthcare ProgramsIn-Hospital Safe Sleep Modeling ProgramChildbirth Educator ProgramDischarge Gift & Logo ProgramHospital Gift Shop, Safety Store & Lactation Center ProgramNational Safe Sleep Hospital Certification
blog
us
uk
My Account
My Wish List
()
Sign Out
Sign in
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyHalo Innovations, Inc. respects your privacy. All personal information you give us is maintained in accordance with our privacy policy and will not be used in ways that are contrary to that policy.
Use of Information
Information collected by Halo Innovations, Inc. about its users is used internally by authorized employees of Halo Innovations, Inc. and it affiliates for the following three main reasons.
1. We collect information, such as a password and address, in an effort to make your shopping experience as quick and easy as possible when returning to our site.
2. We collect information from you to figure out which areas, features and products our users like the most, so we can continue to improve what we offer on our site.
3. We collect information from you so that you can receive and have the opportunity to participate in special offers we may offer from time to time.
General Security
Your credit card, personal information, and password are safe. We use the latest encryption technologies to guard against unauthorized access to your information.
Changes to Your Account
As a registered user of Halo, you can review and change your account information at any time. Refer to "My Account" on the home page.
Changes to Policy
Halo Innovations, Inc. may modify this privacy policy at any time, and such modifications will take place as soon as they are posted. As such, you, the user, agree to review the policy periodically, and your continued access or use of this site shall be under the acceptance of this modified agreement.
Limitations
While we take our privacy policy seriously and do all we can to protect your personal information, we cannot fully ensure that your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties. Such examples include the government or unrelated third parties who may force us to disclose information to them, or third parties who might unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. In addition, if there is ever a case where we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to private entities and law enforcement or other government officials, as we believe necessary or appropriate.
Terms of Use
By using our website, you agree to the Terms of Use policy. To review this policy, click here
Cookie Settings
copyright © 2020 Halo Innovations Inc. all rights reserved.
